Does it matter if you've been living in Istanbul for this work of yours and for the other ones?
It doesn't matter at all.
Would it have made any difference?
It doesn't make any difference
because when we talk about it to people in Istanbul or in Izmir, they support it anyways.
And also since the project is open source;
People in Russia come, they come from the US
and from all Europe and from the whole word, they come and look at it.
And as I said, since it is an open source project, people can become a part of the team.
They can join the project, they can contribute with their code adding to my code.
Anyone, can contribute as well. Anyone, who want to support it and want to help it, can.
They may check out a project and tell us its short comings
We can fix it or they may see the shortcomings and develop it themselves
And hence they can fix the issue. Since the project is open source
they can support no matter which city or country they live in.
Alright, do you think to get a patent of your project?
No, actually, it has only a logo that I like, let me show you
It's a birthday gift to me from an ex colleague called Cenk.
It has a logo like that and I just think of getting patent of this logo.
But it's not very necessary, some other guy can take it and work on it.
Because it's open source, we code it
Logo is a little fun side of it
Actually, I have different plans and projects for the future.
If they go to the webpage and look at it
there is a section called Future in above the Flexible Grid System
And I think of some other things about the future there
The plans extend to a warm workspace like place, a cafe for developers and designers
where they can work while drinking coffee and eating cake
But this is the last step, beforehand,
when people like it and use it, we may make t-shirts, mugs and stickers.
But before I want to build a front-end editor like thing
And at the moment, there is a separate CSS framework. Besides the grid system I'm trying to make a CSS framework
So I always work to make it better
Thank you for joining
Thank you, thanks a lot.